[Heo Seong-jin’s ‘Finish Line’]
[Nervous music]
[Leo] Take it, it’s your father’s.
"Loading"
[Sergey/Russian]
the person who killed your father
[Russian] That gun
I'm the one who handed it to you
Minjooyoung!
[러시아어] 개새끼야
왜 그랬어
왜 그랬냐고!
[Bang Bang]
[Tang]
tell me
Tell me!
[Man] Hey, Leo
- [Dreamy music]
- [shaking]
[Jooyoung’s heavy breathing]
[Bang!]
[dark music]
[Jooyoung] Ugh
you did it
you
Ugh
[Rough breathing]
[Splash!]
[nervous music]
- [Wham - Siren]
- [Detective] Thanks, I just saw it.
Well, they fight amongst themselves.
I guess this is what happened, well
Well, there's nothing more to see.
Now, let’s get organized and sign up.
[Jooyoung] Who is your father?
I know you killed it
Shall I help you?
Who is that?
Ohtala
[sigh]
[Jooyoung] I am your father
I'll help you get revenge
Ottala, who killed your father
There's a police officer watching your back
To get revenge
We have to deal with him first.
[squeak]
[Beep - Camera]
Something like this
I don't think it suits you
[MAX's 'GET IN THE RING']
[Dongju/Narration] Torn and broken
Even if my body breaks
Until you crush your opponent
The king
never die
"Justice"
[Organization member] This bastard, Mr.
[The spirit of the organization members]
[Organization member] You bastard!
[Noisy]
[Dongju] Ugh!
- [Groans of organization members]
- [clatter]
[Seokchun] Ugh!
Are you here to save Emna? huh?
Ouch!
You stupid bastard
Still, it's okay
Even though I lose every time, I come back like this
I didn't come to see you
stupid bastard
Hey! Lee, Mr.
[Organization member’s scream]
[Mansik] Ugh!
[Organizer] Here it is! Come to work!
[Organization member] Lee, Mr.
Oh, ah...
[Seokchun] Let it rot!
Hey!
[Organization member] Hey!
[Jaehong] Hey, hey!
Have you calmed down?
[Mansik] Ugh! ah! ah!
- [Exciting music]
- Hehe
[Organization member] Ugh!
[Mansik] Ah!
Did I do something wrong? I was scared, I was scared
I told you not to come, I told you not to come, Mr.
These foolish bastards
Hey!
- [Organization member] Hey!
- [Mansik] Oh!
- Ugh!
- [Organization member] Ah...
Wow
won, won
Damn you, you won!
- [Intense music]
- This, this...
Oh my, I'm so bored to death
Oh, stop! Mr.
[Organization member, Man-sik] Ugh!
[Mansik] Hey!
Last!
[Urgent music]
- Ah...
- [Swish - knife]
[swish - knife]
[Organization member, Dongju] Ugh!
[Wham - Siren]
[Jooyoung’s heavy breathing]
It's noisy, Mr.
- [Exciting music]
- [Whoop Whoop - Siren]
Yes, this is the SWAT team, what should we do?
Ah...
That's it
All the reporters followed me
It's a bit hard to stay still...
Yes, I understand.
[Call end sound]
Hey, what are you doing?
Quickly stop them from entering!
Jump out there quickly! Stop it!
[The devil's trembling breathing]
[Leo’s soft moan]
[Devil] Come to your senses, come to your senses!
Come to your senses
Can you tell me now?
your real name
Mild fragrance
Mihyang Yoon
It's tacky
[heavy music]
[Leo] I’ll remember
[Russian] Hello, my love
[Crack]
[Mihyang] Ah...
[Nervous music]
[Seokchun] Ugh, Mr.
I heard you did fencing, huh?
But if you are this afraid of knives
What should I do, huh?
Lee, Mr.
[Calm music]
Hey
But did you come alone?
That bastard looks like a child
Oh, where have you been searching already?
He's not the kind of guy who dies that easily.
[Seokchun] That’s how it should be
Because I'm going to cut that bastard's head.
Don't be easy on me
I don't want to admit it, but
more than you guys thought
Because he is much more than expected.
I looked down on you too
I lost everything to him
I don’t like Yoon Dong-ju either.
Do you know what I hate more?
[Seokchun] What?
You lose, whoever it is
To win like that
I ran until I died
What are you muttering to yourself?
If you come now and can't do anything
'Cause I feel so shabby
Are you out of your mind?
So now I don't want to run away
Let's go to the end
Do it again!
[intense music]
Ah!
Ooh, ooh!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Hey, let's stop, hey
Are you a police officer?
If a police officer hits someone, he becomes a child, right?
Right? Is it a child?
They said they came to save Emna.
Why are you fucking with me?
You little leech!
[Noisy]
[Groans from organization members]
[Ding! - Elevator]
[nervous music]
[Loud gunshot]
Ah, Mr.
[nervous music]
[Ding! - Elevator]
[Grumbling]
[Ttogakttogak]
Mr.
Ugh!
Ouch!
[Mihyang] Ah, uh...
[Splendid music]
"Kings Never Die"
[Reporters’ questions]
[Boom!]
[Seokchun’s moans]
[Dongju] Hey!
[Beep - Tinnitus]
Ugh
- Ah, child, Mr.
- [Dark Music]
Mr.
Ah...
[Ding!]
[jumping and jumping]
[Groans of organization members]
[Hannah] Ugh!
[Organization member] Hey!
It's Hannah!
[Organization member] Ugh, ah...
Hey
While I couldn't see you
Your face has become pretty cool, right?
[Jooyoung] You’re not dead yet?
of course!
I'm not dying
Until I catch you, Mr.
- [Organization member] Ugh
- [Puck]
[Organization member] Hey!
[Jooyoung’s spirit]
[Jooyoung] Hey, hey
Hey!
[Mihyang’s heavy breathing]
Are you crazy?
[Mihyang] Goodbye, you crazy bastard.
[Jooyoung] Ugh!
[intense music]
[Jooyoung] Ah, Mr.
[Hannah moans]
[Dongju] Oh my, Mr.
Ah...
[Dongju] It’s Hannah
Are you okay?
Hannah, Ji-Hanna!
Hannah, come to your senses, Ji-Hanna!
Jihanna!
It's noisy, it hurts my ears
[Hannah sighs]
Are you really okay?
Mr...
In such a dangerous place
What if I come alone?
[heavy music]
[Hannah moans]
Dongju Yoon, are you okay?
[Jaehong] Are you okay? I'm bleeding
What about Minjooyoung? Have you seen Minjooyoung?
I'm still alive
Even an ambulance
Shouldn’t this be called, right?
Ha, Mr...
[Groans from organization members]
[Paramedic] Hold on.
[Wham - Siren]
[Mansik sighs]
[Mansik] National University and the police are the same
Why don't you have a good day?
[Mansik sighs]
The mobile squad and fire fighters
I searched the entire building.
I don’t think I found Minjooyoung.
[Jonghyun] I saw you earlier
There are no traces of the transported vehicle either.
I think it's already gone
Ah, it's stuck here
Do you think Minjooyoung has one or two straws?
Everyone must be busy hiding it.
So we have to find it
[Mansik] Us?
Where do you come from on the topic of wanted fugitives?
you just stay still
Oh, just stay still.
What do you do with this bastard?
The key is whether you take him out or not.
Straw?
[Interesting music]
[Jonghyun] Why?
I came here
Minjooyoung heard from someone.
phone
Check your last call history
I guess I know who the straw is.
[Hannah clears her throat]
[Jaehong] Oh, the trash
There's too much inside
[Thump thump]
Okay
Oh, I'm dizzy!
- Ah, anemia!
- [Jaehong] Uh, team leader.
[Dongju] Huh?
[Small] Did you find it?
If you found it, stand up now.
Uh, wake up.
[Mansik] Ugh, it’s tough.
[rattling]
But will this ever be restored?
As long as the SIM chip is ok
Wouldn't it be possible?
I'll leave it to the foreman.
What are you saying?
[Bangbang!]
[Jaehong] Team leader
- [Noisy]
- [Magnificent music]
[Mansik] Hey
[humorous music]
What is it?
[Pan Yeol clears his throat]
[Mansik] Ugh!
Commissioner!
Commissioner, Commissioner...
Huh?
How did your chin get like that?
Yoon!
This...
Where is Yoon Tong-ju?
- Oh, Mr...
- [Mansik] What?
Yoon Dong-ju, you bastard.
[Mansik/Laughing] Ah, Yoon, Yoon Dong-ju
Well, I don't know
- [Panel] ‘Well’? 'well'?
- [Pukpuk]
Really, Mr.
[Panel] You don’t know even if you know, right?
Ha, I'm a bastard!
Just chin up
I should have blown it, really, sir.
I think you police officers have all eaten.
Especially you, you bastard!
you! Don't move here
Hold each one and stand!
Manufacturing new drugs and
It turns out there was...
Hey, hey, if you keep doing this, I'll go out, hey
what how
Is this thing going back? Mr.
A, Mr.
[Car engine sound]
Hey, hey, hey
Oh, what happened?
Did you see the news?
[Seokchun] Ah!
No, what happened?
There's an uproar in the news right now.
Where is President Min now?
Oh, what's wrong with your face again?
Where did this come from again?
Shut up!
Mr. Niga*
Because the truck was sent off late,
Do you know how much the medicines that could not be transferred cost?
Ah, Mr.
[Car engine sound]
[Korean-Chinese] Seongnime
How did it go? Did you recognize it?
Everyone can be contacted.
No son has ever seen President Min.
This looks pretty funny, huh?
[Seokchun’s sigh]
So what should we do with those items?
[dark music]
Even if you beat it up, it would be hundreds of billions.
If you count what has already been moved...
President Min’s contact also became a child.
Even kittens to trade with
Because the year it was made is all over.
Anyone who knows what's in here
Now there's only one guy
Hey, what about the items?
Okay, okay.
and now
How many kids can you save?
Just gather everything you have.
[jumping and jumping]
I'll get back to you
- [Call end sound]
- [Click]
Ah, Mr.
[Chinese] Do you want to go out?
‘Shang’ what?
Ana, Mr.
Don't be a jerk, you bastard.
I'm the heavyweight champion
Do you understand?
Mr.
[nervous music]
- I like fingerprint recognition, hehe
- [Voice guidance] Opened
- [Mansik] Daughter
- Dad!
[News - TV]
Our Jeonga
Dad was worried after watching the news.
- [Mansik’s light smile]
- What are you talking about?
I bought steamed chicken!
[Jeong-ah] Huh? Is it steamed chicken?
Oh, I rather like it.
[Mansik] Of course it would be good, right?
Doing nothing all day
Just rolling around in the corner of the house
What are you doing? Hey, come in
Because we talked a lot
I need to do something like this
- [Jaehong] Hello, Jeonga.
- [Jeong-ah] Ah...
[Mansik] Did you see it last time? say hello
Me, my dad and my co-workers
And here is my daughter Gojeong.
[Click]
[Jonghyun] Excuse me
[Exciting music]
hello
[Mansik] Hey, take the steamed chicken!
- [Mansik] Salty
- [Jonghyun’s sigh]
[Together] Thank you for your hard work
[Soft music]
[Mansik] Ha...
Wrap it in old paper and eat it.
This is amazing
Last time I ate with Jeong-ah.
I kept thinking about it
Wrap this in old paper
So delicious, huh?
It's really delicious
[Jaehong] Is it delicious?
I thought this was softer and more delicious.
Is it delicious? Soft?
[Man-sik] Inspector Ji, I’m a little sad, huh?
Ah, to my father
If there was such a story
Please tell us
Shouldn’t I have given it to you? uh?
Ah, alone
Sighing like that, huh?
I'm slightly, slightly, slightly disappointed, huh?
I'm sorry
It's already going to be hard
Why are you doing this to Hannah?
I need to catch that bastard and kick him.
Stop beating the crap out of me, okay?
Until you are released from the wanted list
Don't move
Just stay at home, okay?
Where are you going, tsk
[Jaehong] Forward
What are you going to do?
We have to catch it
Of course
[Jonghyun] The joint headquarters of the police and prosecutors
I'm in charge of the whole case
It won't be easy for us to intervene.
It will be difficult to receive support.
[Jaehong] Then, let’s go to Gwangsu University.
Just Chief Seo-gang Seo-gang.
Can you move?
[Mansik] Chief Kang’s family
It's going to be a little hard, huh?
I've already been disciplined
Because my hands and feet would have been tied
Then it's just us and Gwangsudae left.
Still...
Oh, stop eating.
now dad
I'm talking about something important
[Jeong-ah sighs]
[Jeong-ah’s deep breath]
- [moktak sound effect]
- Huh? Again, again
Dad
I told you not to do that, huh?
Where did you learn strange things?
Isn't it Lamaze breathing?
Llama?
[Jaehong] This is Lamaze breathing.
It's helpful for mental and physical stability.
My wife used to do it often too.
When our children were pregnant
[humorous music]
Surely you...
[hiccup]
[Mansik] Hey, Gojeong-ah
Hey, Gojeong, open the door.
Oh, let's talk to dad.
Hey, open the door, okay?
Are you really like that?
Did you come to Korea after fighting with your mom?
- [Rattle]
-Open the door, Gojeong!
[Jaehong] Are you okay, team leader?
i lamaze breathing
I'm talking for no reason
[Dongju] No
[Jaehong sighs]
[Jaehong] Ah, but everyone
Is it okay if I don’t go to the hospital?
[Jonghyun] Oh, I’m fine.
we're okay too
[Jaehong] Then let’s go home
I really am today
I feel like I'm so desperate for home
That's right
I'm on my way, I'll take you there.
I love it so much
But what about two?
Go in carefully, we'll go first.
[Jaehong] Ah
- Our hug
- [Jonghyun] Let’s go.
[Jaehong] Uh, uh
I'll go
[Calm music]
[Click]
[Jaehong clears his throat]
Honey, I'm here
Were you very worried?
Honey, you know what?
I was so embarrassed by that bronze medal.
I feel like I didn't do my best
I feel like I've always lived like that
Never once to my kids
I couldn't show it proudly
[Jaehong’s wife] Huh?
ah!
[Jaehong’s wife] Hey, me and my kids too
you have never
I've never felt ashamed
I saw you on the news
How much the kids liked it
whatever you decide
me and my kids
I always support you
Ha...
- Oh, why are you crying, really!
- [Jaehong] Ah, ugh, ah...
[Dongju] Didn’t it hurt?
wait and see
here
[Hannah] Yoon Dong-ju
[Dongju] Huh?
You've been unconscious for two days
Were you worried?
Let's go to the hospital first.
I'll go and see where I can.
Hey, you're fine, huh?
I took a deep breath and woke up
Rather, I feel refreshed
I am you
I wish I thought of you a little more
[Calm music]
Don't hold back when it really hurts
Okay, okay, okay
You come first
[Hannah] Just do it roughly
It's not that bad
[Dongju] Huh?
If you leave things like this, it will be a disaster
Leave it to me
This is something I specialize in
Ah, you are
Should I go to the hospital tomorrow?
Okay
Now
I did it all
Oh, why are you so good?
I
Have you ever said anything like that?
I was beaten a lot when I was young.
Whenever my dad drinks, he beats me like that.
bullying my mom
And then
What I can do for my mom
This was all I had
Apply medicine to the wound
Do it like this
So I'm used to this
Why?
Just proudly
Then give me a prize
Change your clothes
What are you doing? I'm going to take it off soon.
Huh?
- [Dongju] Ah
- Fish oil, hey.
[Soft music]
- [Stopping music]
- [Beep beep - door lock]
- [Beep beep beep beep]
- [Hannah Mo] Oh my, it’s Hannah!
- Hey, hey, hey, hurry up, hey.
- [Hannah Mo] Hannah, mom!
- [Dongju] Ah...
- [Hannah] Hannah, are you inside?
- Cell phone, password, oh my.
- [Humorous music]
[Beep beep beep beep]
Ugh, why doesn’t this open like this?
What should I do, oh my
- [Hannah] Uh, ah, not here.
- [Dongju] Where...
Tue, restroom, restroom
[Hannah Mo] Let’s focus, Kyungsook.
Focus, you can do it
I'm a mom! Mom, it's Hannah.
- Hannah, please, Hannah.
- [Beep beep - door lock]
-What should I do with my daughter?
- [Beep beep beep beep]
Mom, why doesn't this open like this?
Oh my
Oh my, Rain, did you change your password?
He, oh my
Hey, are you okay? uh?
Where are you looking, where are you looking?
Oh God, thank you
Oh, look!
No, why is your face like this?
- Wow
- Just a little scratched.
Why did you come?
just watch the news
My heart is pounding
Doesn't it look like it's going to jump?
No, and why aren't you answering the phone!
I'm leaving my mom behind, really.
Uh, where else are you, huh?
Are you hurt anywhere else?
- Uh, uh, no, no, no.
- [Kyungsook] Oh my, here...
[Hannah] It’s okay, calm down, uh, uh
[Kyungsook] It’s okay, what’s okay?
[Sigh] Oh, what should I do?
Oh my
-Why is your face so hot, huh?
- [Soft music]
Well, what's hot? Well, it's the same
Oh my gosh, just stay still.
Oh, what should I do with this, huh? Hey
[Hannah] Ah! ahhh
[Kyungsook] Oh my, what’s wrong, oh my!
Where does it hurt?
Oh, my head hurts a bit.
Oh, and it hurts a little, I
[Kyungsook] Where and why does it hurt?
- Oh my, what should I do?
- Take me to my room, take me to my room.
Yeah yeah
First, grab your mom, mom, okay?
Leaning on mom like this
- [Hannah] Wow
- [Kyungsook] Wow, I really am
No, your dad
What are you doing in the sky?
You're not protecting me, really, oh, really
What is all this about?
Oh, really
Uh oh, boy, Mr.
[Super owner] Hey, can you come out of there?
[People laughing]
Where are you going!
[Ding dong ding dong]
[Thump thump thump]
Sergeant Jonghyun Kim
Sergeant
No, bro
Jonghyun, please open the door, bro.
brother
[Clap]
[Voice guidance] Opened
Have you been to the sauna?
don't laugh like that
Excuse me
[Guide voice] Locked
Are you moving?
Help me?
Stop being interested, stop pretending to be friendly.
I said that because I was curious.
Since when did you hate me so much?
from the beginning
Why?
I hated smiling
[bright music]
[Jonghyun] Yoon Dong-ju?
[Player] Oh, you know?
Boxing idiot selected for national team this time
If you run 100 laps here
They say they believe in the superstition that winning a gold medal is like that.
Hey, for a week.
I do that every day
Everyone fell asleep on lap 94.
But I think I'll succeed today
It's already the 99th lap
Look at his sweat, wow, fighting Dongju Yoon!
- Hey, Yoon Dong-ju, we're here!
- [Woman] Fighting!
[Player] Wow, Dongju Yoon is cool!
[People cheering]
- I'll go.
- [Player] Uh
Man, this is amazing, really, huh?
Plays really well
[People cheering]
[Jonghyun] I hated smiling
It's still like that now
Who knows what's good?
[Jonghyun] Grow up
sleep well
[Click]
[Dongju] Wow, wow
[Dongju chuckles]
[Shoo - Susan]
Wow, wow.
[Crunches]
[groan]
[Shoot - Toilet]
[Jonghyun] Minjooyoung
Have you found it yet?
[Daeyong] Oh, on the road CCTV
With the Russian mafia
Those Korean-Chinese kids from the Northeast Association
It was confirmed that he escaped.
How did Min-young Min run away?
I don't know
The road to Kinmen Central
It's the only place here
Seeing that there is no trace so far
Obviously help from the police
I would have received it
[Daeyong] Ah...
I need to find that straw guy quickly.
It's a pain in the ass
There is a truck that was confiscated yesterday.
It was J9's representative Oh Jong-gu.
The rest of the trucks
It was caught on CCTV
I can't identify the license plate
I think it was all used to transport candy.
thank you
please send me these pictures
We'll take care of Oh Jong-gu's side.
yes
But why is it like that, that thing?
[Thumb - Wind]
[Jaehong] Did you have trouble sleeping?
Because of what happened yesterday?
Our Jeonga?
They said I wasn't pregnant
[Jaehong] Oh!
Oh, thank goodness.
I was really worried
[Mansik] My wife got pregnant.
Oh, sister-in-law, huh?
[Jaehong’s laughter]
Wow, congratulations, really.
No, still
Do you have that much strength left?
Oh, just eat good food alone, really.
[Jaehong’s laughter]
I tied it up
tight
[Jaehong] Ah...
No, then my sister-in-law is having an affair...
[humorous music]
The wind is blowing
[Mansik’s sobs]
The wind is blowing!
[Jonghyun] Let’s go
[Jaehong] Sergeant Kim, I’m taking your car...
Uh, why isn't this...
Sergeant Kim, Sergeant Kim, I’m uncomfortable!
[Team Leader] Wow, you came at the right time?
Thank you for lending me your car
Just that?
no
Everything the team leader did for me
[bright music]
Why should I help you?
Please ask someone else
[Hannah] I have no one to ask for.
The person who talks to me at the office
It's just the team leader.
kid, so
Do you need me to listen? why?
Team leader, you like me.
Me? I think I'm misunderstanding something!
Even if it's a misunderstanding, I'd like to ask
Someone to trust
That's because there's only one team leader.
[Hannah] And
sorry for me
It's okay
at home for 3 months
Rolling around watching TV, whatever.
Ah
It's unfair to just come out
I secretly took it out
At the founding ceremony of the joint prosecution and police headquarters
List of people in attendance
I thought it might help with the investigation.
Why are you so kind to me?
I said I like Hanna
[Calm music]
That's right, I like it
I was jealous even though I was jealous
In the past, I too
I wanted to run on the field.
Like Hannah
[Team leader’s awkward laughter]
So I'm vicariously satisfied now.
Oh my
Like watching the main character in a drama
While teaching
[Team leader laughs]
Ah, sir, I already cleaned it up and ran away, tsk.
[Mansik] Is there anything?
Have you been using the office?
It seems like it's been a while
The electricity is all cut off.
[Mansik] Ah, these guys, really
[Call connection tone]
Not the cars here
I think the license plates are all different too.
The shape of the storage box is also different.
[Jaehong] Team leader, I checked with the district office.
Delegating registration of scrap vehicles for cargo commercial use
There is a junkyard.
Oh, representative vehicles
illegally expunged there
I think they used the license plate number.
Let's go there first.
[Exciting music]
[Woman/Laughing] Should I do it or not?
Should I do it or not?
[Mansik] President Yongju Lee
[Yongju] What is it? Ah, Mr.
[Jaehong] Huh?
I went by KTX
No, I'm Oh Jong-gu's accounting clerk.
[Mansik] Ah...
[Yongju] What is it? Are you my dad and my brother?
police
child, Mr.
[Jaehong] Oh my, oh my, oh my
[humorous music]
- [Dongju] Uh huh
- [Yongju] Ah, Mr.
What, why, where are you running away?
- Oh, oh, oh!
- [Dongju] Ayu, aha, bastard
[Yongju] Ah!
Ah, Mr.
- A, Mr.
- [Dongju] Huh?
Put down the knife
[Yongju] Ah!
ah!
To CEO Oh Jong-gu
Did you sell cargo commercial license plates?
Let's check the vehicle numbers.
how do i remember that
Not just one or two business partners
Just the truck license plate I put on it.
There must be more than a hundred
Just grab it
All you have to do is go and pay the fine.
What are you doing with something like this?
Do you come to me feeling embarrassed?
Take it away!
Oh, take it...
[Mansik] Wait a minute
Hey, you have a daughter?
- Yes
- Are you married?
yes
[Mansik] Then the married bastard
Here, bar, bar...
[Mansik’s trembling breathing]
- Are you cheating on me?
- [Jaehong] The team leader’s eyes roll...
[Kyungri] Hey,
I know that
[Gyeongri] Ugh
[Interesting music]
Separately managed by the representative
I'm the manager of cargo vehicles.
[Mansik] Illegal vehicle
There are about 15 in total.
[Jonghyun] Uh, transporting candy.
The vehicle used is
There are 7 units in total.
[Mansik] Ha, but Oh Jong-gu, this bastard
Where on earth have you gone?
Minjooyoung
I won't give up candy
If you chase candy
Oh Jong-gu and Democratic Yeongdo
I can catch them all
While looking through the CCTV
Here are the cargo vehicles
Let’s investigate them one by one.
[Mansik] Yes, jumping with your feet again
I have to look for it.
[Jonghyun] I’ll take a picture of this
- [Mansik] Okay
- [Click]
Now
Let's divide into two teams and move on.
And you wait here
Oh, why?
[Mansik] Why, why, you bastard?
you are still wanted
If you stand out and become a problem,
It's a pain in the ass
no
What am I
Even if you stay still
Although it has a striking appearance
Well, you just have to go quietly.
You're going to be so quiet
You just stay here
Just report the situation to me.
-What kind of situation am I in...
- [Jonghyun] I’ll go with Dongju.
- It's more dangerous to leave you alone.
- [Mansik] Do you want to do that?
her!
[Mansik] That’s right
Yes, Sergeant Kim takes him.
Even if I get into an accident
It's better to have Sergeant Kim by your side.
Oh, what about accidents, am I a child?
[Mansik] You’re worse than a child, you bastard.
Ugh, you're a wanted fugitive, huh?
Don't nag
Just hurry up when I let you go
- [tuk]
- Hurry up, man.
[tuk]
[Mansik] Oh, wait a minute.
Come to think of it
Sergeant Kim, aren’t you wearing glasses?
[Gwangse] Huh?
[Pawn shop owner] Because I took it off
You look bigger
I will follow you
[Jaehong] That’s right, the character lives.
Life is the same, whatever
come out
[Gwangse] Both of them are handsome
[Man] Oh my, why are you like this!
Ouch! Ugh! Ugh!
[dark music]
- [Beep - Tinnitus]
- [Man's scream]
That's the license plate I bought there too.
Hey, I've never met Oh Jong-gu.
Why do you run away if you don't know, yes?
No, I said it was the police.
[Jonghyun] Let’s check the license plate
[Man] Me too a few days ago
I bought it because it happened.
I'm the victim, I'm
[Jonghyun] I understand
Thank you for your cooperation
What do you say?
a few days ago
He was also tricked into buying a license plate.
[Bang - car door]
If I'm tired, I rest here.
I'll go the rest of the way alone
No, who said it was hard?
I'm different from anyone else
Do you have stamina of steel?
Just here
Don't bother me later
no
You hate me like this
Why did you say you would go with me?
Because I care
What?
What's with Hannah and me?
uh
[Dongju] Ah!
Well...
I like it and hate it, Mr.
- [Sigh]
- [Calm music]
- [Shoot - Susan]
- [Dongju] Wow, wow
[Dongju chuckles]
[Dongju moans]
- [Wing - Cell Phone]
- [Sigh]
Yes, captain.
[Forensic team leader] In the office,
There are many eyes to see
worked here
You can rest assured because it’s my brother’s place.
Now
[Hannah] Hello
[Forensic inspector]
Hey, the damage was severe.
Still, half of the data was saved.
- [Laughter from the inspector]
- thank you
[Mansik] Lastly,
What number did you call?
- [Meaningful music]
- [Dongju] Huh?
'4723'?
4723?
- why? Do you know the number?
- [Knock Talk]
- [Call connection tone]
- [Interesting Music]
- [Voice guidance] Your call is...
- [Mansik] Huh? Lee Jong-hoon?
Who was it? Who was it?
I'm the youngest at Gwangsu University.
[Mansik] Just stay still
It finally makes sense now
The day Dongju was kidnapped
The area of operation is
We only shared it with Gwangsu University.
Oh Jong-gu
It was strange that he suddenly appeared there.
[Jaehong] Then
The fact that the gun was taken away by the devil
Was this intentional?
I don't know, since when
First of all, this guy is a fraud.
Come to think of it, the day the devil ran away
That day too
Even the guy who was watching the devil
I was the youngest at Gwangsu University.
[Jonghoon] Let me just wait a moment
While going to the bathroom
It's gone
Ha, Mr.
- [Mansik] Oh, Daeyong.
- [Substitute] Yes
- [Mansik] Are you with the youngest?
- Our youngest?
I'm on probation
that before
My gun was taken away when I was escorting the devil.
But why about our youngest?
[Mansik] Okay, now I found the straw.
- [Wham - Siren]
- All you have to do is catch Minjooyoung.
Hey, it's spectacular.
I sent a lot too
[Jonghyun] By special order from the Commissioner
Only the experience invested
They say there are over 500 people.
Commissioner, at the police headquarters
We even provide accommodation and meals.
[Mansik] Ah, that guy
Did I eat something wrong?
It was like this and then like that
The attitude change is very fast.
[Mansik] He uses it to say that the game has been turned upside down.
Oh, by the way, Minjooyoung
Where did this bastard hide?
Huh? I'm running around like that.
Can't you see a single hair?
상놈의 새끼
[어두운 음악]
[윙 - 휴대 전화]
어, 대용아, 막내 찾았어?
[Wham - Siren]
[Detective 1] Jong-hoon, it’s not you!
[Detective 2] Does this make sense?
- [Mansik] Hey
- [Detective 2] What is this, you bastard!
[Man-sik] What happened to that kid?
[Daeyong] I don’t know
- We also came here after being reported.
- [Detective 2’s crying]
There’s no way Jonghoon would do that.
something is wrong with this
[Detectives] Hey, Jong-Hoon!
When Minjooyoung leaves Geummun
It must have been difficult to avoid people's eyes.
Ha, even police and fire personnel.
I was crushed
Ah, Mr.
How did you escape?
[Meaningful music]
[Jonghyun] By special order from the Commissioner
Only the experience invested
They say there are over 500 people.
[Mansik] Ah, that guy
Did I eat something wrong?
It was like this and then like that
[Jaehong] Commissioner, at the police headquarters
We even provide accommodation and meals.
[Dongju/Inner thoughts] You coward
[Dongju] Minjooyoung
I think I know where it is
Those guys
When you feel danger, you instinctively
hide in the safest place
Among the people who were there at that time
The most powerful guy
Have you contacted the mayor?
[panel] Ah, yes
They said they would send someone soon.
Would you like some tea?
There is good green tea
[Mobile Unit] You must not enter.
Get out of the way
Ha, what are you doing now...
Let go, you bastard.
What! Why stop it now?
[Mobile Unit] You must not enter.
[Dongju] What are you doing now?
Let it go or not?
Ah, what are you doing, why are you stopping me, now!
[Mobile leader] What are you!
- [Beep beep - radio]
- Hey, block it underneath!
What should I do to stop it now?
Ah, why are you blocking this now?
What are you doing now, yes?
- Come out, come out, quickly.
- [Noisy]
By whose instructions now
Is this what you are doing, yes?
Come out
I will be held legally responsible for this later.
Come out, quickly.
- [Jonghyun] Ask for legal responsibility
- [Mansik] Let go, let go!
[Noisy]
[Dongju] Let go, Mr.
[Nervous music]
[Panel] Oh my!
Ah, hey
I was hiding here
You coward
[Mobile leader] Commissioner!
Ugh!
Hey, put the gun down, nigga, put it down! Tsk
Hey, what are you doing?
Put it down, put it down, put it down
Hey, hey, hey
They say you're going down, down, down, down
He said he was coming down, clean it up.
Ah, Mr.
[panel opening] Huh?
[Nervous music]
[Panel heat] Ugh
Hey Jihanna!
Put the guns down, put them down
Jihanna, put the gun down, put it down!
Get down! I, Mr.
Who do you want to see die?
[Bang!]
Ah! Ah...
[Panel groans]
[Mobile leader] Commissioner!
Commissioner, Commissioner!
Did you hear the gunshot? gunshot, gunshot
We all have to go up together
Now, one, two, three, let's go!
[Mansik] Come out!
[Roaring roar]
- [panel opening] Ah!
- [Mobile Forces] Ugh!
[Panel] Hey, hey
Don't touch me, don't touch me
Sergeant Kim!
[기동대] 업어, 업어, 업어
- [기동대원] 천천히
- [판열의 아파하는 신음]
[판열] 야, 야, 야, 살살 해
이놈의 새끼야
왜 이래요?
Captain Jihanna fired the gun.
Go quickly, Mr.
[Mobile Leader] Ah, Mr.
- quickly, quickly
- [Panel] Go slowly
[Mobile Forces] Ugh!
- [Panel] Go quickly, quickly
- [Substitute] Gun?
- I see.
- [Jaehong] You can shoot
Yeah, well, what can I do?
I see.
[Call end sound]
[Dongju] Hey, where are you running, Mr.
[Jooyoung] Ah!
[nervous music]
Do you have insurance?
[Jooyoung] Ah, Mr.
[Dongju] If there is no
Let me introduce you to someone I know well.
From now on
You're going to break a lot, huh?
[laughter]
[Jooyoung’s difficult breathing]
[Jooyoung] Ah...
Even after being so devastated
Are you okay?
Do you think you made fun of me?
Shut up and wake up
[sigh]
[Jooyoung] What I overlooked was
It's not me, it's you
Ugh
[Squeak!]
Ah, Mr.
[Bangbang!]
Dongjuya
Ah...
[Jonggu] Hey, where are you going?
Hey, Mr.
I thought you ran away
It appears like this
Why am I running away?
you are here
[Jonggu’s laughter]
[Dongju moans]
[Meaningful music]
[Jonggu] Ah...
Stop it, man
I'm so tired, you bastard.
Just, oh, really, shit.
Huh?
[Jonggu] Ah...
child
- [Ringing sound effect]
- What?
Are you sure you can't see it?
[Dongju] What bullshit are you talking about?
[Jonggu] Hey
Wow
That's right
I really can't see this guy
[Calm music]
you me
Didn't I tell you not to raise your blood pressure?
When the Master speaks
This bastard should have taken note, Mr.
Yes, I have it
Would you like to play a game with me?
[Dongju’s difficult breathing]
[clatter]
Mr. [Dongju]
Ugh!
[Emotional music]
[Hannah] Senior!
Yoon Dong-ju!
[Mansik] Stop!
Ah...
Commissioner
This kind of shit happened
Do you just stay still?
[Daeyong] But our youngest is
I don't think so
There's another rat.
[Daeyong] That rat
You're on my team
How did I come out?
[Mansik] What you have
Money isn't everything?
No, what if it's not money?
Let's just ask one guy.
[Dongju] He will make the first move
[Mansik] Minjooyoung Lee
Through Gumyeon Intersection
I'm moving to Gumyeon-dong
[Dongju] Do you think I was that precious?
[Hannah] How long will you stay with me?
Are you going to pretend like nothing happened?
[Jooyoung] Look forward to it
[Dongju] Hanna, are you going?
[Jooyoung] Very today
It's going to be an impressive day
[Heo Seong-jin’s ‘Finish Line’]